Kabir,

React web app developer.

Address: Laxmipur, Bangladesh.

Github: https://github.com/kabirshuvo

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/kabirshuvo19/

E-Mail: kabirshuvo19@gmail.com

Phone: +8801717515631;

Experienced working with teams to produce impactful, leading-edge websites that engage customers and deliver business results. Demonstrated **success** in identifying and resolving complex code issues.

<u>Skills:</u> Expertise: React, Node.js, HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, React-Bootstrap, Tailwind-CSS. Headless-UI.

Comfortable: Firebase, Nodejs, Express, and MongoDB. Tools: Axios, Redux-toolkit, Tanstack-Query,

and Framer-Motion. database Management, Documentation, TypeScript, NextJs, and others.

<u>Projects:</u> cyco.tv: A MERN Stack Team Project for movie streaming with live TV.

This is my Last **team** project. As an architect's decision, we decided to go with **MERN**

Stack, the whole team expert in .this technology. Till Now we added almost 20-25 functionalities and some others are in progress. Now we are shifting .this Mern to **NEXT.JS** to generate another **salable** Product.

You are welcome to visit .this site: https://cyco-inc.netlify.app/

Summer Craftify: A MERN Stack Project for a Summer School.

Key-Features: *Multi-User Dashboard – Conditional for **Admin**, Instructor and users.

*Appointments, selected classes, and Enrolled classes collection.

*Real-time update and stripe payment system integrated.

Tech-I-Used: Axios, Tanstack-Query, Framer-motion, Tailwind-css etc.

Live-Site-Link: https://summercraftify.web.app/

Github-Repo: https://github.com/kabirshuvo/summerCraftify-client

Kinder Kids: Another MERN Stack Project for Toys Market Place.

Key-Features: *Firebase **Authentication** with Aesthetically Good looking Web **app**.

*Simple CRUD Operations...

*Real-time update and stripe **payment** system integrated.

Live-Site-Link: https://kinder-kids-b9263.web.app/

Github-Repo: https://github.com/kabirshuvo/kinder-kids-kingdom-client

Work History:

Junior Web Front-End Developer | W3aSolutions && August 2022 - Present, && Remote.

I'm working as a Junior Web **Front-End** Developer at w3aSolutions on a contract basis. My primary role is writing project proposals for would-be clients and **developing** the first look of a web app. If we get the project approval then I work until it is deliverable.

2017-02 - 2020-04: Technical Analyst cum Junior Executive || Amarstock, Dhaka.

I worked with Amarstock for **3** years long. In Amarstock I played a **double** role. My main job was to train people how to use amarstock.com web app and what they will get from that site. Besides this, I also worked as a junior executive, in **administration**.

Education:

2004-2008 Bachelor of Social Science | Public Administration | University of Rajshahi. Bangladesh.

Certifications:

2023-06-2023-07: 7 weeks bootCamp;

2023-01 – 2023-06: Complete Web Development Course at Programming Hero – [6months]

2017-01-2017-04: Search Engine Optimization – [3months]